http://www.sunspaces.com/privacy-policy.html

HOME
HOT TUBSHomeSelf-CleanSerenityShop by SizeFeaturesPhoto Gallery
SWIM SPASHomeAquaTrainerAquaSportExecutiveAquaPlaySpecificationsPhoto GalleryVideosSwim Spa Covers
COMMERCIAL SPASHomeH600-C: 5 PersonH800-C: 8 PersonH1000-C: 10 PersonH1100-C: 11 PersonH1200-C: 12 PersonSpa ComparisonsPhoto GalleryCodes & RegulationsComponents & AccessoriesGuide to Hot Tub SelectionWarrantySUNROOMS & OTHERSAcrylic SunroomsSunroom KitsSunroom GalleryAcrylic AwningsAcrylic SkylightsPergolaDecks & RailingsWood WorkingSPA ENCLOSURESHomeOpen AirSemi EnclosedFully Enclosed
SPA ACCESSORIESSpa AccessoriesHot Tub CoversSwim Spa CoversCover LiftersStepsSafety & ConvenienceRepair & Parts
CONTACTContact usAbout usSite MapOLD WEBSITE
250-652-0888
make a site for free
Privacy Policy
SKYVIEW INDUSTRIES LTD is committed to respecting the privacy of individuals in the treatment of personal information and to the principles outlined in this Privacy Policy, which is developed in compliance with British Columbia’s Personal Information Protection Act (“PIPA”). PIPA sets out the rules for how organizations such as ours can collect, use and disclose your personal information. We recognize that the people with whom we do business and our employees have a need for the appropriate management and protection of any personal information that individuals agree to provide to us.
Personal information means information about an identifiable individual, such as someone’s name, home address, social insurance number, sex, income or family status.
This Privacy Policy applies to this website and all products and services offered by SKYVIEW INDUSTRIES LTD. We will only collect, use or disclose personal information in accordance with PIPA.
Personal Identification Information
We collect personal identification information from individuals in a variety of ways in connection with activities, services, features or resources we make available on our website. Individuals may visit our website anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from individuals only if they consent to the collection, use or disclosure of such information, except where we are legally authorized or required by law to do so without consent. Individuals can consent orally, in writing or electronically, and consent may be implied or express depending on the nature and sensitivity of the personal information.
Individuals may withdraw their consent at any time, by giving SKYVIEW INDUSTRIES LTD reasonable notice, and can always refuse to supply personal identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website related activities.
Why we collect and use information
SKYVIEW INDUSTRIES LTD may collect, store, use and retain personal information about individuals (clients, suppliers, employees, etc) in order to better manage its business. We will make all reasonable efforts to fully inform individuals about the planned use/disclosure of their personal information. SKYVIEW INDUSTRIES LTD will limit the collection and use of personal information to that required for valid business purposes, for example, to verify identity or credit-worthiness, to provide requested services or products, or to comply with legislation.
SKYVIEW INDUSTRIES LTD will only collect and use personal information that is necessary to fulfill the purposes identified in this Policy. We will not collect, use or disclose personal information except for the identified purposes, unless we have received further consent from the individual.
In addition to the care that SKYVIEW INDUSTRIES LTD takes directly, we are also working with all of our partner organizations that may at some point handle personal information gathered by us in the course of their relationship with and service to us. Each third party partner has agreed to meet our standards of privacy, confidentiality and security.
All employees and third party staff who in any way handle or manage personal information have acknowledged and agreed to adhere to our privacy code and the procedures that support that code.
Disclosure
SKYVIEW INDUSTRIES LTD will not disclose personal information unnecessarily to employees or any third party, unless the effected individual consents. We do not sell, trade, or rent individuals’ personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.
Accuracy
SKYVIEW INDUSTRIES LTD will make every reasonable effort to ensure that the personal information collected and used is accurate and complete. Individuals providing personal information have the right to access their personal information, and will have the opportunity to review and correct their personal information, and on written request by the individual to whom the information relates, SKYVIEW INDUSTRIES LTD will modify the information as required.
Retention and Storage
SKYVIEW INDUSTRIES LTD will retain personal information for as long as necessary to fulfill the identified purposes or as long as required for a legal or business purpose. This period may be related to legislation. SKYVIEW INDUSTRIES LTD will store personal information using hard copy and/or electronic means in such a way as to prevent unauthorized collection, access, use, disclosure or disposal of the personal information.
Changes to this privacy policy
SKYVIEW INDUSTRIES LTD has the discretion to update this Privacy Policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage individuals to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy periodically and become aware of modifications.
Your acceptance of these terms
By using this website, you signify your acceptance of this Policy. If you do not agree to this Policy, please do not use our website. Your continued use of the website following the posting of changes to this Policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
Contacting us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this website,
or your dealings with this website, please contact us.
Individuals who are not satisfied with SKYVIEW INDUSTRIES LTD’s response, can complain to the Office of the Information and Privacy Commissioner for British Columbia.
This document was last updated on February 18, 2012
Address
Skyview Industries Ltd1 - 6721 Butler Crescent
(off Keating Cross Road)
© Copyright 2020 Skyview Industries Ltd - All Rights Reserved
